Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Central Region Freight Joint Area Committee Transcript Records 1954-2010 IBT0053
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1994, June 14-15 (Box 159, Folder 1)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1994, June 15 (Box 159, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1994, August 23-24 (Box 159, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1994, August 25 (Box 159, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1994, September 12 (Box 159, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1994, September 13-14 (Box 159, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1994, September 13-14 (Box 159, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1994, September 13-14 (Box 160, Folder 1)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [1 of 2], 1994, September 13-15 (Box 160, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting [2 of 2], 1994, September 13-15 (Box 160, Folder 3)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1994, September 14 (Box 160, Folder 4)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1994, September 14 (Box 160, Folder 5)
- Alcohol and Drug Committee Meeting, 1994, September 14 (Box 160, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Hearings Meeting, 1994, September 15 (Box 160, Folder 7)
- Central Regional Meeting, 1994, October 10 (Box 160, Folder 8)
- Arbitration Committee Meeting, 1994, December (Box 160, Folder 9)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1994, December 12 (Box 160, Folder 10)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1994, December 12 (Box 160, Folder 11)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1994, December 12 (Box 160, Folder 12)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1994, December 13 (Box 160, Folder 13)
- Deadlocked Cases Meeting, 1994, December 13 (Box 161, Folder 1)
- Deadlocked Cases Meeting, 1994, December 13 (Box 161, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1994, December 13 (Box 161, Folder 3)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1994, December 13 (Box 161, Folder 4)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 1994, December 13-14 (Box 161, Folder 5)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1994, December 14 (Box 161, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Cases Meeting, 1994, December 15 (Box 161, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1995, February 16 (Box 161, Folder 8)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1995, March 13 (Box 161, Folder 9)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1995, March 13 (Box 161, Folder 10)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1995, March 14 (Box 161, Folder 11)
- Joint Committee Meeting, 1995, March 14 (Box 161, Folder 12)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1995, March 14 (Box 161, Folder 13)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 1995, March 16 (Box 161, Folder 14)
- Arbitration Hearing Meeting, 1995, March 16 (Box 161, Folder 15)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1995, April 11 (Box 161, Folder 16)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1995, April 11 (Box 161, Folder 17)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1995, June 12 (Box 161, Folder 18)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1995, June 12 (Box 161, Folder 19)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1995, June 12 (Box 161, Folder 20)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1995, June 13 (Box 161, Folder 21)
- Central Area Committee Meeting, 1995, June 13 (Box 161, Folder 22)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1995, June 13 (Box 161, Folder 23)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 1995, June 14 (Box 161, Folder 24)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 1995, June 14 (Box 161, Folder 25)
- Arbitration Hearings Meeting, 1995, June 15 (Box 161, Folder 26)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1995, June 29 (Box 161, Folder 27)
- Special Change of Operations Meeting, 1995, August 8 (Box 161, Folder 28)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1995, September 11 (Box 161, Folder 29)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1995, September 11 (Box 161, Folder 30)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1995, September 11 (Box 162, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1995, September 12 (Box 162, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1995, September 12 (Box 162, Folder 3)
- Central Committee Meeting, 1995, September 12 (Box 162, Folder 4)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1995, September 13 (Box 162, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1995, September 14 (Box 162, Folder 6)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1995, November 13 (Box 162, Folder 7)
- Special Committee Meeting, 1995, November 13 (Box 162, Folder 8)
- Arbitration Committee Meeting, 1995, November 27 (Box 162, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1995, December 4 (Box 162, Folder 10)
- Central Region Committee Meeting, 1995, December 4 (Box 162, Folder 11)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1995, December 4 (Box 162, Folder 12)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1995, December 4 (Box 162, Folder 13)
- Change of Operations Cases Meeting, 1995, December 12 (Box 162, Folder 14)
- Change of Operations Cases Meeting, 1995, December 12 (Box 162, Folder 15)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1995, December 15 (Box 162, Folder 16)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1996, March 11 (Box 162, Folder 17)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1996, March 11 (Box 162, Folder 18)
- Grievance Hearings Meeting, 1996, March 12 (Box 162, Folder 19)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1996, March 12 (Box 162, Folder 20)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1996, March 12 (Box 162, Folder 21)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1996, March 12 (Box 162, Folder 22)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 1996, March 12 (Box 162, Folder 23)
- Management Association Committee Meeting, 1996, March 13 (Box 163, Folder 1)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1996, March 13 (Box 163, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1996, March 13 (Box 163, Folder 3)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 1996, March 14 (Box 163, Folder 4)
- Arbitration Committee Meeting, 1996, March 14 (Box 163, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1996, April 10 (Box 163, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1996, April 10 (Box 163, Folder 7)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1996, June 10 (Box 163, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1996, June 10 (Box 163, Folder 9)
- Drug Discharge Committee Meeting, 1996, June 10 (Box 163, Folder 10)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 1996, June 11 (Box 163, Folder 11)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1996, June 11 (Box 163, Folder 12)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1996, June 13 (Box 163, Folder 13)
- Arbitration Cases Meeting, 1996, June 13 (Box 163, Folder 14)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1996, September 9 (Box 163, Folder 15)
- Central Area Committee Meeting, 1996, September 9 (Box 163, Folder 16)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1996, September 9 (Box 163, Folder 17)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1996, September 9 (Box 163, Folder 18)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1996, September 9 (Box 163, Folder 19)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1996, September 9 (Box 163, Folder 20)
- "Forty and Out" Committee Meeting, 1996, September 11 (Box 163, Folder 21)
- Arbitration Hearings Meeting, 1996, September 12 (Box 163, Folder 22)
- Arbitration Hearings Meeting, 1996, October 31 (Box 163, Folder 23)
- Discharge Hearings Meeting, 1996, October 31 (Box 163, Folder 24)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1996, December 9 (Box 163, Folder 25)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1996, December 9 (Box 163, Folder 26)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1996, December 9 (Box 163, Folder 27)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1996, December 9 (Box 163, Folder 28)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1996, December 9 (Box 163, Folder 29)
- Central Area Committee Meeting, 1996, December 9 (Box 163, Folder 30)
- "Forty and Out" Committee Meeting, 1996, December 11 (Box 163, Folder 31)
- Central Cartage Company Meeting, 1997, January 9 (Box 164, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1997, March 4 (Box 164, Folder 2)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1997, March 5 (Box 164, Folder 3)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1997, March 10 (Box 164, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1997, March 10 (Box 164, Folder 5)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1997, March 10 (Box 164, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1997, March 10 (Box 164, Folder 7)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1997, March 10 (Box 164, Folder 8)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1997, March 11 (Box 164, Folder 9)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1997, March 11 (Box 164, Folder 10)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1997, March 11 (Box 164, Folder 11)
- "Forty and Out" Committee Meeting, 1997, March 11 (Box 164, Folder 12)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1997, March 11 (Box 164, Folder 13)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1997, March 12 (Box 164, Folder 14)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1997, June 9 (Box 164, Folder 15)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1997, June 9 (Box 164, Folder 16)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1997, June 9 (Box 164, Folder 17)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1997, June 9 (Box 164, Folder 18)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1997, June 9 (Box 164, Folder 19)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1997, June 9 (Box 164, Folder 20)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1997, June 10 (Box 164, Folder 21)
- "Forty and Out" Committee Meeting, 1997, June 11 (Box 164, Folder 22)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1997, September 8 (Box 164, Folder 23)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1997, September 8 (Box 164, Folder 24)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1997, September 8 (Box 164, Folder 25)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1997, September 8 (Box 165, Folder 1)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1997, September 8 (Box 165, Folder 2)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1997, September 8 (Box 165, Folder 3)
- "Forty and Out" Committee Meeting, 1997, September 9 (Box 165, Folder 4)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1997, September 9 (Box 165, Folder 5)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1997, September 10 (Box 165, Folder 6)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 1997, September 11 (Box 165, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1997, November 5 (Box 165, Folder 8)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1997, November 5 (Box 165, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1997, November 5 (Box 165, Folder 10)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1997, November 5 (Box 165, Folder 11)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1997, November 6 (Box 165, Folder 12)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1997, December 8 (Box 165, Folder 13)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1997, December 8 (Box 165, Folder 14)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1997, December 8 (Box 165, Folder 15)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1997, December 8 (Box 165, Folder 16)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1997, December 8 (Box 165, Folder 17)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1998, March 9 (Box 165, Folder 18)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1998, March 9 (Box 165, Folder 19)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1998, March 9 (Box 165, Folder 20)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1998, March 9 (Box 165, Folder 21)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1998, March 9 (Box 165, Folder 22)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1998, March 10 (Box 165, Folder 23)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1998, June 9 (Box 165, Folder 24)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1998, June 9 (Box 165, Folder 25)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1998, June 9 (Box 165, Folder 26)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1998, June 9 (Box 165, Folder 27)
- Drug and Alcohol Discharge Committee Meeting, 1998, June 9 (Box 165, Folder 28)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1998, June 9 (Box 165, Folder 29)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1998, June 10 (Box 165, Folder 30)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1998, June 16 (Box 165, Folder 31)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1998, September 11 (Box 166, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1998, September 11 (Box 166, Folder 2)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1998, September 11 (Box 166, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1998, September 11 (Box 166, Folder 4)
- Special Discharge Committee Meeting, 1998, September 11 (Box 166, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1998, September 24 (Box 166, Folder 6)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1998, September 28 (Box 166, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1998, September 28 (Box 166, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1998, September 28 (Box 166, Folder 9)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1998, September 28 (Box 166, Folder 10)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1998, September 28 (Box 166, Folder 11)
- Special Circumstance Committee Meeting, 1998, September 28 (Box 166, Folder 12)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1998, September 30 (Box 166, Folder 13)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1998, December 15 (Box 166, Folder 14)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1998, December 15 (Box 166, Folder 15)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1998, December 15 (Box 166, Folder 16)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 1998, December 15 (Box 166, Folder 17)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 1998, December 15 (Box 166, Folder 18)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1998, December 15 (Box 166, Folder 19)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1998, December 15 (Box 166, Folder 20)
- "Forty and Out" Committee Meeting, 1998, December 16 (Box 166, Folder 21)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 1998, December 16 (Box 166, Folder 22)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, February 11 (Box 166, Folder 23)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1999, March 9 (Box 166, Folder 24)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1999, March 9 (Box 166, Folder 25)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 1999, March 9 (Box 166, Folder 26)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1999, March 9 (Box 166, Folder 27)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, March 9 (Box 166, Folder 28)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1999, March 9 (Box 167, Folder 1)
- Change of Operations Grievance Committee Meeting, 1999, May 18 (Box 167, Folder 2)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1999, June 15 (Box 167, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, June 15 (Box 167, Folder 4)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 1999, June 15 (Box 167, Folder 5)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 1999, June 15 (Box 167, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1999, June 15-16 (Box 167, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1999, June 15-17 (Box 167, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, June 18 (Box 167, Folder 9)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, June 18 (Box 167, Folder 10)
- Change of Operations Grievance Committee Meeting, 1999, August 10 (Box 167, Folder 11)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, August 10 (Box 167, Folder 12)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1999, September 2 (Box 167, Folder 13)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, September 2 (Box 167, Folder 14)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1999, September 2 (Box 167, Folder 15)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 1999, September 2 (Box 167, Folder 16)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 1999, September 2 (Box 167, Folder 17)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1999, October 5 (Box 167, Folder 18)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 1999, October 5 (Box 167, Folder 19)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, October 5 (Box 167, Folder 20)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1999, October 5-6 (Box 167, Folder 21)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1999, October 5-6 (Box 167, Folder 22)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1999, October 5-6 (Box 167, Folder 23)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 1999, November 16 (Box 167, Folder 24)
- Change of Operations Grievance Committee Meeting, 1999, November 16 (Box 167, Folder 25)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 1999, December 14 (Box 167, Folder 26)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 1999, December 14 (Box 167, Folder 27)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 1999, December 14 (Box 167, Folder 28)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 1999, December 14-15 (Box 167, Folder 29)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 1999, December 14-15 (Box 167, Folder 30)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 1999, December 14-15 (Box 167, Folder 31)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2000, March 14 (Box 167, Folder 32)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2000, March 14 (Box 167, Folder 33)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2000, March 14 (Box 167, Folder 34)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2000, March 14 (Box 167, Folder 35)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2000, March 14-15 (Box 168, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2000, March 14-15 (Box 168, Folder 2)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2000, June 13 (Box 168, Folder 3)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2000, June 13 (Box 168, Folder 4)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2000, June 13 (Box 168, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2000, June 13 (Box 168, Folder 6)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2000, June 13-14 (Box 168, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2000, June 13-15 (Box 168, Folder 8)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 2000, September 12 (Box 168, Folder 9)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2000, September 12 (Box 168, Folder 10)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2000, September 12 (Box 168, Folder 11)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2000, September 19 (Box 168, Folder 12)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2000, September 9 (Box 168, Folder 13)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2000, September 19 (Box 168, Folder 14)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2000, September 19 (Box 168, Folder 15)
- Over the Road Committe Meeting, 2000, September 19-20 (Box 168, Folder 16)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2000, September 19-20 (Box 168, Folder 17)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2000, November 30 (Box 168, Folder 18)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2000, November 30 (Box 168, Folder 19)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2000, December 5 (Box 168, Folder 20)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2000, December 5 (Box 168, Folder 21)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2000, December 5 (Box 168, Folder 22)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2000, December 5 (Box 168, Folder 23)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2000, December 5-6 (Box 168, Folder 24)
- Special Committee Meeting, 2001, January 18 (Box 168, Folder 25)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2001, March 13 (Box 168, Folder 26)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2001, March 13 (Box 168, Folder 27)
- Deadlocked Drug Cases Meeting, 2001, March 13 (Box 168, Folder 28)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 2001, March 13 (Box 168, Folder 29)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2001, March 13 (Box 168, Folder 30)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2001, March 13-14 (Box 169, Folder 1)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2001, March 13-14 (Box 169, Folder 2)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2001, May 15 (Box 169, Folder 3)
- Drug Committee Meeting, 2001, May 15 (Box 169, Folder 4)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2001, May 15 (Box 169, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2001, May 15 (Box 169, Folder 6)
- Primary Dispatch Committee Meeting, 2001, May 15 (Box 169, Folder 7)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2001, May 15-16 (Box 169, Folder 8)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2001, May 15-16 (Box 169, Folder 9)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2001, September 11 (Box 169, Folder 10)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2001, September 11 (Box 169, Folder 11)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2001, September 11 (Box 169, Folder 12)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2001, September 11 (Box 169, Folder 13)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2001, September 11-12 (Box 169, Folder 14)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2001, September 11-12 (Box 169, Folder 15)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2001, November 20 (Box 169, Folder 16)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 2001, November 20 (Box 169, Folder 17)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2001, November 20 (Box 169, Folder 18)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2001, November 20 (Box 169, Folder 19)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2001, November 20 (Box 169, Folder 20)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2001, December 3 (Box 169, Folder 21)
- Central States Committee Meeting, 2001, December 4 (Box 169, Folder 22)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2001, December 4 (Box 169, Folder 23)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2001, December 4 (Box 169, Folder 24)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2001, December 4 (Box 169, Folder 25)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2001, December 4-5 (Box 169, Folder 26)
- Change of Operations Grievance Committee Meeting, 2001, December 5 (Box 170, Folder 1)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2001, December 5 (Box 170, Folder 2)
- Grievance Committee Meeting, 2001, December 5 (Box 170, Folder 3)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2002, March 12 (Box 170, Folder 4)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2002, March 12 (Box 170, Folder 5)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2002, March 12 (Box 170, Folder 6)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2002, March 12 (Box 170, Folder 7)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2002, March 12 (Box 170, Folder 8)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2002, March 12-13 (Box 170, Folder 9)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2002, March 12-13 (Box 170, Folder 10)
- Iron and Steel Committee Meeting, 2002, March 13 (Box 170, Folder 11)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2002, June 11 (Box 170, Folder 12)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2002, June 11 (Box 170, Folder 13)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2002, June 11 (Box 170, Folder 14)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2002, June 11 (Box 170, Folder 15)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2002, June 11-12 (Box 170, Folder 16)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2002, June 11-12 (Box 170, Folder 17)
- Local Cartage Deadlocked Cases Meeting, 2002, June 11-12 (Box 170, Folder 18)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2002, September 10 (Box 170, Folder 19)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2002, September 10 (Box 170, Folder 20)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2002, September 10 (Box 170, Folder 21)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2002, September 10 (Box 170, Folder 22)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2002, September 10-11 (Box 171, Folder 1)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2002, November 12 (Box 171, Folder 2)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2002, December 10 (Box 171, Folder 3)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2002, December 10 (Box 171, Folder 4)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2002, December 10 (Box 171, Folder 5)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2002, December 10 (Box 171, Folder 6)
- Maintenance of Standards Committee Meeting, 2002, December 10 (Box 171, Folder 7)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2002, December 10 (Box 171, Folder 8)
- Change of Operations Committee Meeting, 2003, March 11 (Box 171, Folder 9)
- Special Circumstances Committee Meeting, 2003, March 11 (Box 171, Folder 10)
- Drug and Alcohol Committee Meeting, 2003, March 11 (Box 171, Folder 11)
- Joint Area Committee Meeting, 2003, March 11 (Box 171, Folder 12)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2003, March 11-12 (Box 171, Folder 13)
- Over the Road Committee Meeting, 2003, March 11-12 (Box 171, Folder 14)
- National Intermodal Committee Meeting, 2003, April 9 (Box 171, Folder 15)
- Local Cartage Committee Meeting, 2003, June 10 (Box 171, Folder 16)